boxofficereport.net 2012-01-26

# Privacy Policy | BoxOfficeReport.net

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

 **Google Adsense and the Other Advertisers Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the Google Ads cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htm>l Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. We Can Not Control The Cookies Set By these Ad Networks

 **Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting BoxOfficeReport.net, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
